OK.
好的。
Now let's go through our real example of Aaron's we should be very comfortable with how to describe
现在让我们来看看我们真实的亚伦例子，我们应该很熟悉如何描述
household chores and the words related to doing laundry.
家务劳动和与洗衣服有关的词语。
We should be pretty comfortable with some of the phrases that we use to describe errands.
我们应该对我们用来描述差事的一些短语感到满意。
But let's actually look at how we can put them into practice with a real example.
但是，让我们通过一个真实的例子来看看我们如何将它们付诸实践。
OK.
好的。
Yesterday I had to run to yo Mart.
昨天我不得不跑到 yo Mart。
I just made up that name.
我只是编了这个名字。
I don't think there's a real yo mark to pick up a few things we need.
我不认为有一个真正的哟标记来拿起我们需要的一些东西。
I bought vegetables and eggs for a dish.
我买了蔬菜和鸡蛋做一道菜。
I'm planning to cook tonight dishes one sort of thing I want to cook a dish I'm planning to cook tonight.
我打算今晚做一道菜我想做一道我今晚打算做的菜。
I also grabbed some milk and eggs because we were running low on both.
我还拿了一些牛奶和鸡蛋，因为我们都快吃完了。
We're running low on both milk and eggs.
我们的牛奶和鸡蛋都快用完了。
My wife asked me to get some chocolate.
我的妻子让我去拿一些巧克力。
So I bought her a few Dove chocolate bars and I also got several big cartons of almond milk for the
所以我给她买了几块多芬巧克力棒，还买了几大盒杏仁奶
week.
星期。
That means we probably drink several cartons of almond milk in one week in one week.
这意味着我们可能会在一星期内喝几盒杏仁奶。
Maybe it's Monday OK.
也许是星期一好吧。
A carton is something usually made of cardboard or paper and it has a liquid inside orange juice milk
纸箱通常由纸板或纸制成，在橙汁牛奶中含有液体
on the way home I stopped by the U.P.S. store stopped by the U.P.S. store to drop off a package I need
在回家的路上，我在 U.P.S.被 UPS 拦下的商店存放我需要的包裹
to send to my friend in Colorado so to drop something off is to go to a place to stop by a place usually
寄给我在科罗拉多州的朋友，所以送东西就是去一个地方，通常在一个地方停留
for a short time maybe only a couple of minutes and leave something there to drop off a package at the
很短的时间，也许只有几分钟，然后在那儿留下一些东西，以便在
U.P.S. store I'll be there tomorrow I'll drop it off I can only stay for a minute and then I need to
UPS。商店 我明天会在那里 我会把它放下 我只能停留一分钟然后我需要
go.
去。
OK sure sure.
确定确定。
Drop it off.
把它扔掉。
Could you drop it off later.
以后能不能放下。
Yeah.
是的。
No problem.
没问题。
So it's usually something that happens quickly and it's the opposite of pickup.
所以这通常是很快发生的事情，它与皮卡相反。
We can use it also when we're talking about the train station situation.
当我们谈论火车站的情况时，我们也可以使用它。
I need to go to the train station to drop off my friend.
我需要去火车站送我的朋友。
I have to drop off my kids at school drop off my kids at school.
我必须把我的孩子送到学校 把我的孩子送到学校。
OK.
好的。
So I stopped by the U.P.S. store to drop off a package.
所以我停在了美国邮政总局。商店投递包裹。
I need to send to my friend in Colorado my friend in Colorado.
我需要把我在科罗拉多的朋友寄给我在科罗拉多的朋友。
So we've used most of the phrases that we learned just before this.
因此，我们已经使用了在此之前学到的大部分短语。
Again they're very very common.
同样，它们非常常见。
I hope that you can pay attention to how they're used and try using them yourself.
希望大家可以关注一下它们的使用方式，自己尝试使用。
Next time you describe your routine.
下次你描述你的日常生活。
OK.
好的。
So to practice this try using the phrases that we learned to describe Aaron's to describe or explain
所以要练习这个尝试使用我们学到的描述亚伦的短语来描述或解释
the errands that you need to run today or tomorrow or sometime maybe this week.
您今天或明天或本周某个时候需要执行的差事。
Be very detailed if you want to explain it to a friend.
如果您想向朋友解释，请非常详细。
Record yourself.
自己记录。
Record yourself doing it and speaking naturally trying to use these phrases and then listen to the recording
录制自己的动作并自然地尝试使用这些短语，然后听录音
again so that you can catch small mistakes and work on improve your speaking habits.
再次，以便您可以发现小错误并努力改善您的口语习惯。
Recording is a great way.
录音是个好方法。
As I've said several times before to help yourself get in the habit of catching small mistakes and fixing
正如我之前多次说过的，帮助自己养成发现小错误并改正的习惯
those things.
那些事。
It's a great way to improve your awareness awareness.
这是提高您的意识意识的好方法。
All right.
好的。
Good luck.
祝你好运。
See you in the next lesson.
下节课见。